ckbproducts.com 2005-03-08

# Privacy Statement

**Disclosure of information:**

All personal information is obtained for the purposes of completing  
transactions.  We will never give or sell your information to a third party nor disclose any information pertaining to any transaction.

**We will never disclose:  
**Your name (in whole or in part)  
Your address  
Your phone number  
Your email address  
Your billing information  
Your personal preferences as to what you like to buy

**Tracking information:  
**We do use software to track purchases but this information is only used in cases of fraud.  
We do not use software to obtain your email address after visiting our site but  
you may choose to join our [Mailing List](http://www.ckbproducts.com/mailing_list.htm)

We believe your personal information is exactly that:  
YOUR INFORMATION.

We will never use YOUR INFORMATION as a marketing weapon or to earn a buck at your expense. 

**When   placing an order is my personal information safe and confidential?  
**YES!  **Safe and Confidential using SSL!**  
During a Secure SSL session, data passed back and forth between your computer and our server is secured by using key cryptography. Your computer exchanges key information with CKBProducts computers to create a private conversation that only your computer and our system can understand.  All credit card transactions have added security because they are broken into two (2) parts, scrambled, then sent through 2 different secure databases where we must match the two parts up before processing your order.

**Other Products:**   [Wholesale Automotive]  [Wholesale Briefcases]  [Wholesale Cutlery]  [Wholesale Electronics]  [Wholesale Flatware]  [Wholesale Giftware]  [Wholesale Houseware]  [Wholesale Jewelry]  [Wholesale Kitchenware]  [Wholesale Knives]  [Wholesale Luggage]  [NEW ITEMS]  [Wholesale Sporting Goods]  [Wholesale Tools]

**Important Links:   ** [About Us]  [CATALOG]  [Contact Information]  [Dropship Policy]  [Frequently Asked Questions]  [Increase Auction Sales]  [Join Mailing List]  [Out of Stock List]  [Privacy Statement]  [Return Policy]  [Track Your Order]
